Map Collection
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Cabinet 2
  - City of Hartford, Connecticut. Hartford: Metropolitan District, 1995, 32.5 x 29 in. (Drawer 4, Folder 1)
  - 1992 Voting Districts of Hartford. Hartford: Metropolitan District, 1992, 38 x 24 in. (Drawer 4, Folder 1)
  - June 2002 City of Hartford Senatorial, Assembly and Voting Districts. City of Hartford Department of Housing and Community Development. Hartford: City of Hartford, 2002, 29.5 x 22 in. (Drawer 4, Folder 1)
  - 17 Hartford Neighborhoods. City of Hartford Department Development Services, Planning Division. Hartford: City of Hartford, 2004, 34 x 24 in. (Drawer 4, Folder 1)